[Knock at door]
Nick?
It’s Mummy and Daddy, dear.
Welcome to Casa de Nick.
Your mother thought  she'd just pop over,
and check the place out.
Come on, let's go.
What's wrong, Mum?
Aww. Tears of joy...
To see her son doing so well.
Stop it!
Be strong.
No, I'm fine.
Just overwhelmed at how...
lovely your place is.
Cool.
Well, let me give  you the grand tour.
This is the kitchen.
This is the living room.
This is the dining room.
This is the master bedroom.
So many rooms.
And where’s the loo?
Oh, dear God.
No, Mum.
That's just for the  leak in the ceiling.
Loo’s through there.
Of course.
I'll just go and freshen up.
Hold on.
What are you doing?
Well, I've only got one bulb,
so I have to move it  from room to room.
Never mind.
Eugh. I'm fine.
Cool, eh?
You know, I’m thinking of  making a few improvements.
Maybe taking out this wall.
You do that one more time  and you’re a dead man.
Good old Viv.
It’s that sort of relationship.
Anyone for tea?
Oh, lovely. That would be nice. No! Lovely...
Oh, I've missed you.
I've missed you.
I don't believe it.
My son is struggling to survive in this desolate hellhole,
and all you're going  to do is watch the telly.
I’m not going to  watch it, Susan.
I'm going to take it home.
The telly’s not the only  thing that's coming home.
No, no you don't.
No way.
No. For the first  time in his life,
Nick is standing on  his own two feet.
But he's standing  in excrement!
[Knocking on door]
Get down!
Don’t make any noise.
Hey, Harper.
You owe me rent.
I know you're in there.
I saw the light, you lazy  son of a pig's nipple.
For your information,
that's the pig's nipple  you're referring to.
And no one is allowed to  speak about my son that way,
except me.
I've earned it.
Dad-
It’s alright, Nick.  I'll handle this.
And as far as a shameful  excuse for a flat goes,
you're very lucky to get a  penny of his hard-earned money.
But, Dad-
Quiet, Nick.
So, the next time you ask for rent, I suggest you ask politely.
Believe me, you don't want  me on your bad side.
I'm a dentist.
Oh, Ben.
That was wonderful.
Except the part about  the pig's nipple.
There's no reason to  shout at Nick like that.
Actually, he has.  I lost my job at the pub.
I'm a week behind  on my rent,
and I haven't eaten  for two days.
Ohhh!
Well, if there's  anything we can do.
Come on, Susan, let's go.  Sounds like Nick's busy.
So, are you gonna pay?
No, he's coming  home with us.
Cool, I'll just  get my things.
No!
Wait.
Let's just think about  this because, look...
What sort of lesson  would it be if we let Nick
give up every time  life gets difficult?
You know, I mean, if it means me having to pay a month's rent
just to keep him here,
that's a sacrifice I'm willing to make.
And 100 up front to  cover the damages. Cash.
Yep, yep. Fine. Fine.
Damages?
This flat is a masterpiece.
As a matter of fact,  when I get home,
I'm gonna do up the  entire house just like it.
Hurry up with  the money, dear.
Cheque for the rent  will be in the post.
Bye, dear.
Love what you've  done with the place.
Thanks, mate.
Same time next month?